Every time the rain no longer
falls, and I see the sky,
I think back to when I was a child.
Who could only cry?
Blindly chasing after him,
I fell far behind my only thought.
One day I will be stronger.
Bridery and gratitude.
Fading with the wind.
Am I stronger now than I was before?
Or as weak as back then?
I don't know for sure.
But until I do, my voyage will not end.
No matter what's next, I'm
walking straight ahead.
So let's go, there's nothing
that can stop us now.
Those times are on our side,
we'll never let it pull us down.
And we may fall, but we'll
always keep on standing.
There's no way anything will take
what I hold dear away from me.
The voices inside me push
me to keep surviving.
I'll go on, I'll get through,
no matter what I gotta do.
The fiercest of the ball can pour upon me.
I don't care why in the
world would I turn back?
So let's go.
There's nothing that can stop us now.
Though time's not on our side,
we'll never let it pull us down.
And we may fall.
But we'll always keep on standing.
There's no way anything will take
what I hope you're away from me?
I know the future's there for us to see.
We're up against him too,
the legendary hero god.
We didn't make it all the
way here just to lose.
To an old man, legends
ain't nothing but words.
I might say the same
thing to you. White beard.
Your glory days are
just a dying memory now!
Oh, please!
Damn, are you gonna
destroy this entire city?
Send me the bill for
repairs when we're done.
Keep pushing toward the scavenger!
Ironic, I know, but I
forgot about those things.
No more lasers for today. That's enough!
Did you think we were weak, please?
We're from the new world!
Now's our chance!
Get to the scaffold!
A final moment of regret?
Poor boy.
Gold Roger?
Yeah, of course I know who he is.
But who gives a crap?
People talk like he's something
special, but what did he even do?
He just riled up a bunch of criminals.
And thanks to that bastard,
the entire world is screwed up.
And what does that mean?
There's no way you're that stupid.
Everyone knows before he was executed,
he told some BS story
about hidden treasure
to give the middle
finger to the government.
But either way,
it worked,
because a bunch of dumb pirates bought
into the whole thing and went nuts.
Don't you get it?
He left behind a stain
people still can't clean up.
Even killing the bastard wasn't enough.
Now, thanks to him,
we gotta put up with a
bunch of human garbage
pissing on everyone
else following his lead.
He's the biggest piece
of crap who ever lived.
He stinks even after we flushed him.
Just like you, kid.
Huh?
Oh, did I hurt your wittle feelings?
Are you in the Roger fan club?
You got something you want to say, kid?
You start in trouble again, Ace?
What was it this time?
Everyone's making a fuss about some thugs
that got beat near to death by a kid.
That's too bad I was
hoping they would die.
Don't give me that you
realize when you pull this
kind of crap I'm the one
who gets chewed out for it.
Right.
Hey are you listening?
Honestly I don't know what that old fool
was thinking leaving a
boy like you with me.
What you want me to tell you about Roger?
He was
a liar
and a murderer
and a miserable thief to boot.
Only jackasses believe his crap.
King of the pirates king of the chumps.
He's dead.
Either way got that right.
Roger huh?
I'm trying to enjoy a drink over here kid.
The man was a hack.
Now piss off.
You hear me? Beat it, kid.
Hey!
What do you think you're
doing, you little punk?
I should see the other guy, right?
Look, Ace.
You can't keep doing this, kiddo.
So your grandson
He's around my age, huh?
Do you think he's happy with himself?
Luffy, I think he is.
The boy's growing up in fine feather.
Old man Yeah
Tell me the truth.
Did I deserve to be born
or was it just a mistake?
That's not for me to say.
You just keep living
and hope you find out.
Quick carry straw boy back to the ship!
It's not ideal, but we'll have
to save Ace Boy without him.
Eva
Calm down, take it easy.
I need one last favor from you.
We're coming for you, Ace.
We're taking you home.
And Amy never stood a chance.
This is wrong.
My friend, don't lose hope.
I swear, I shall save your life no
matter how much blood it's filled.
We're almost there.
There's no stopping us now.
Don't let them get you down, Ace.
Yeah, we won't leave you.
We're brothers, we stick together.
Damn it, this is all wrong.
How the hell am I supposed to feel?
Pops, Luffy, my friends?
They're here to save me, but!
They're pushing through a sea
of their own blood to do it.
Don't say one last anything!
We're getting out of here alive, darn it!
You know what I need?
I'm sick.
These are tears of joy.
Even after all I've done?
I want to live!
Captain Buggy?
He's awake.
He's alive.
I knew it all along.
Aw, jeez, what happened? We okay?
Aokiji just froze you solid.
It was really freaky.
Oh, no!
You hear that, Navy?
Buggy's coming for you.
No walls, eyes, or giant magma
fists can stop me. Awesome!
You've only been defrosted
like a couple of minutes,
but you're like BAM let's do it.
That's how I roll
Okay, seriously now what
better move my punk?
Son of a
The ravages of time humble us all.
Yes, even you.
Screw the fight.
This is what I was afraid of.
I don't want no sympathy.
There's no way I'm wearing this
crap in front of my enemies!
Damn it, pops.
Wouldn't turn your back
on me if I were you.
You're gonna make the same mistake.
Someone has to see you off and that
duty seems to have fallen on me.
Pops, no!
Oh, got good. Oh, crap.
Another hormone shot?
Do you want to die?
You're past your limit.
I'm sorry, kid, but you've been burning
your candle at both ends for too long.
Have you forgotten that
poison you suffered through?
You cheated death once.
I didn't save you so you
could destroy yourself.
I told you this last time.
My hormones aren't a magic fix-me-up you
can take every time something goes wrong.
I want to save Ace Boy, just like you.
But if you keep misusing my
power like this, you'll die.
As long as I do everything I can.
I don't care if I die.
I'm begging you, you have to let me fight.
Guys, I think Pops is down.
Marco, Geoise.
If I don't keep fighting!
And they kill Ace because
I wasn't there for him?
Then I'd rather be dead anyway.
Right now?
How is the only fight
that matters? Live or die!
You dummy!
Whatever would I tell your dear old dad,
Dragon, if I let you die like a dog
due to my deadly Devil Fruit power?
This stubbornness of
yours is not cute at all!
Ace.
Oh fine, it's your life
give us a good show
Wait, what are you doing?
He's got back up.
No way.
Kizaru hit him dead on.
It's a miracle he's even alive, let
alone getting up and screaming like that.
Luffy.
Remember, Straw Boy, energy
hormone may get you pumped for now.
But if you fall again, that's it.
You're a dead boy. Got it?
Crap, it's happening.
Hold on a sec.
You're not executing Ace while I'm around.
The kid's crazy,
but it isn't like he's going to change
his mind under these circumstances.
Yes, I might as well give
him some backup then.
Hold on, Straw Boy!
He was coming for you!
He's over there!
Straw Hat's still alive!
Not for long, he's not!
I'll finish him off!
Enough crap.
You're not taking another step.
We've got you surrounded now.
Yeah, he's right, there's no
way you can defeat all of us.
The navy always wins.
You might as well give up.
Incoming!
Death!
We?
My, what a fanciful strike.
Thanks, Eva, I owe you.
Kobe!
All right, focus.
If I want any hope of
growing stronger as a Marine,
I have to fight all enemies,
no matter who they are.
This is war.
I'm sorry, Luffy, but I'm
gonna have to kill you.
Now save!
Looks like I got carried away again.
I'm useless after all.
I guess it's back to the truck, Bart.
I knew again!
Those dirty frauds
impersonating my friend!
Monkey D. Luffy.
Why can't they just move?!
Hey, what do you think you're doing?
Boa Hancock, one of the seven warlords.
Navy ally detected.
Ceasing attack. Oh, yeah.
You guys are on the same side.
Thanks a bunch, Hancock.
Isn't that the pirate, Empress?
Have you two got a thing
going on I should know about?
He said it.
He said my name, and he didn't
get it wrong. Please move.
You are standing in the
way I never gave you
permission to address me in such a matter.
Hold on, Pops, coming to save you!
It went straight through.
Yeah, just try and stop me?
Well, that certainly throws
a wrinkle into my plan.
Regeneration, huh?
So that must be why they
call you the Phoenix.
Hey, give me a hand, will you?
Sea Prism Stone?
Oh, it hurt that time, huh?
They got Geoise too.
He's frozen solid.
That's two commanders down.
What should we do now?
Take out the head and
the body will follow.
He's in danger.
Hold still, you monster!
You fool, I will not be chained.
Good, now close in fast!
Against the others and attack
quite big with all you've got.
We'll save him!
No, stay back!
You punks really think that's
all it takes to defeat me?
Just a few toy swords and guns?
I could tear you all apart single-handedly,
but you know that, don't you?
Because you quake when you
hear the name Whitebeard!
No,
no, no, no, no,
no,
no.
That's insane!
I'm not such a fool.
I know what will happen if
I falter, even for a moment.
What will happen if I die?
And knowing that cold truth
I can't allow myself to submit!
Not until the bitter end
So I'll wait until I've taken
care of the future for my sons?
Got it, Ace.
Oh, Pops.
Ah, old fools lost it.
What the hell?
Damn, and we were so close, too?
Bastards have formed a barrier
around Whitebeard's back!
You want us to bury you with the old man?
Your mockery does not sway my honor.
It is our pride and our
joy to stand beside him!
You bunch of fools!
Get away.
Concerned about the future?
I'll be more than happy
to show it to you now.
Let's end this.
Execute him!
Ace, go!
I'm too slow!
Don't make me laugh!
You think I can't stop
those ruts from doing it?
From the start, this was the only way!
Yes!
Don't do it!
Don't you dare!
It's not over yet!
Did you just do what I think you did?
It's the Conqueror's spirit.
Well, damn.
This is a mess.
There's a surprise for you.
Why that little brat?
AAAAAAHHHHHHHHHH!